Baby
I’m just trying to play it cool
I'm just trying to play it cool
But I just can’t hide that
but i just can’t hide that
but i just can't hide that
I want you
Wait a minute, what is this?
Wait a minute 何これ?
Wait a minute 이게 뭐지?
Wait a minute, ¿qué es esto?
Wait a minute 这是怎么回事?
My heart’s going lub-dub
私の心臓が lub-dub
내 심장이 lub-dub
Mi corazón hace lub-dub
我的心脏 lub-dub
Just keeps on pounding
鳴りつづけてる
자꾸만 뛰어
No para de latir
总是跳个不停
Even from afar—oh my gosh!
遠くからでも oh my gosh!
저 멀리서도 oh my gosh!
Incluso desde lejos, oh my gosh!
就算离得很远 oh my gosh!
Pulling me close—you’re my crush!
引っ張られるの you're my crush!
끌어당겨 you’re my crush!
Me atraes, you’re my crush!
也吸引着我 you're my crush!
Like a superpower
超能力みたい
초능력처럼
Como una fuerza supernatural
就像超能力
My heart feels like a giant magnet
巨大な磁石になったみたい my heart
거대한 자석이 된 것만 같아 my heart
My heart parece un gran imán
仿佛是巨大的磁铁 my heart
Everything about you sticks to my heart, boy
君の全てが 私の心にくっついちゃうの boy
네 모든 게 내 맘에 달라붙어버려 boy
Todo sobre ti se adhiere a mi corazón, boy
你的一切紧紧贴着我的心 boy
We’re magnetized, I admit it
We’re magnetized 認めるよ
We’re magnetized 인정할게
We’re magnetized, lo admito
We're magnetized 我承认
This time I want
You You You You like it’s magnetic
You You You You like it's magnetic
U U U U U U U U super attractive
U U U U U U U U super 引力
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
U U U U U U U U super atractivo
U U U U U U U U super吸引力
You You You You like it’s magnetic
You You You You like it's magnetic
U U U U U U U U super attractive
U U U U U U U U super 引力
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
U U U U U U U U super atractivo
U U U U U U U U super吸引力
Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da Dash-da
Like it’s magnetic
Like it's magnetic
Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da
Baby don’t say no
Baby don't say no
Completely opposite, our type
正反対みたい our type
정반대 같아 our type
Son completamente opuestos, our type
似乎正好相反 our type
You’re J and I’m so P
君はJ 私は完全にP
넌 J 난 완전 P
Tú eres J y yo soy totalmente P
你是J 我完全是P
S and N, polar opposites
S極とN極だけど
S와 N 극이지만
S y N, son polos opuestos
S和N是两极
But that’s what pulls us in
だから惹かれるの
그래서 끌리지
Pero por eso nos atraemos
所以才彼此吸引
I’ll make it a green light
してみせる green lightに
내가 만들래 green light
Voy a crear una green light
我会创造出green light
Girls gotta have guts!
女は度胸っていうでしょ
여잔 배짱이지
Las chicas tienen que ser valientes
女人就要有魄力
So let’s go let’s go
So let's go let's go
Let’s go let’s go
Let's go let's go
Don’t wanna hide it, the magnet in my heart
隠したくない 磁石のような my heart
숨기고 싶지 않아 자석 같은 my heart
No quiero ocultarlo, es como un imán, my heart
不想隐藏磁铁般的my heart
Gonna follow my feelings and get with you, boy
心が惹かれるままに 君に向かって行くよ boy
내 맘의 끌림대로 너를 향해 갈게 boy
Voy hacia ti según lo que diga mi corazón, boy
我会跟着心的吸引力走向你 boy
We're magnetized, I admit it
We're magnetized 認めるよ
We’re magnetized 인정할게
We're magnetized, lo admito
We're magnetized 我承认
This time I want
You You You You like it’s magnetic
You You You You like it's magnetic
U U U U U U U U super attractive
U U U U U U U U super 引力
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
U U U U U U U U super atractivo
U U U U U U U U super吸引力
You You You You like it’s magnetic
You You You You like it's magnetic
U U U U U U U U super attractive
U U U U U U U U super 引力
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
U U U U U U U U super atractivo
U U U U U U U U super吸引力
No push and pull
Gonna R.U.N to you
全速力で君のもとへ行くよ
전속력으로 너에게 갈게
Voy hacia ti a toda velocidad
我要全力奔向你
(In a rush in a rush)
Our chemistry
Yeah I’m in too deep now (Baby you’re my crush you’re my crush)
私はすっかり夢中 この瞬間に (Baby you’re my crush you’re my crush)
난 과몰입해 지금 순간에 (Baby you’re my crush you’re my crush)
Estoy completamente absorta en este momento (Baby you’re my crush you’re my crush)
我过分投入在此时此刻 (Baby you're my crush you're my crush)
No push and pull
No regrets, gonna zero in on you
君に集中 後悔はしない
네게 집중 후회는 안 할래
Me enfocaré en ti, sin arrepentimientos
专注于你 我不会后悔
(Gonna dash gonna dash)
Never holding back
Straight ahead, yeah
一直線に yeah
직진해 yeah
Voy directa, yeah
直线前进 yeah
This time I want
You You You You like it’s magnetic
You You You You like it's magnetic
U U U U U U U U super attractive
U U U U U U U U super 引力
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
U U U U U U U U super atractivo
U U U U U U U U super吸引力
You You You You like it’s magnetic
You You You You like it's magnetic
U U U U U U U U super attractive
U U U U U U U U super 引力
U U U U U U U U super 이끌림
U U U U U U U U super atractivo
U U U U U U U U super吸引力
Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da Dash-da
Like it’s magnetic
Like it's magnetic
Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae Bae
BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE BAE
Dash-da-da Dash-da-da
Baby don’t say no
Baby don't say no